Subtitles by explosiveskull
M_I_SForEver
CJ Entertainment Presents
A Moonlight Film and
Perfect Storm Film Production
Executive Producer
Young-Ki Cho
Produced by Jong-Bin Yoon
Myung-Chan Kang
Young-Hoon Kim
Jung-Woo Ha
Nam-Gil Kim
You tell me that you're
still looking for one,
but why should
I believe you? Huh?
I told you, I don't care what it
costs... Just get it done.
And I also told you,
my job depends on it...
Can you please try harder?
Ina, you're going to like
our new house.
It's really quiet and there's
so much fresh air...
The doctor said that it's
perfect for you.
It'll do you good...
Once you you get used to it,
I'm sure you'll like it. Hm?
Sweetie, did you know that...
that new doll
is a limited edition?
It was really hard to find.
I thought you would love it.
Written and Directed by
Kwang-Bin Kim
Ina!
Sweetheart.
You can't just run away.
I was looking
everywhere for you.
Ina, that's our new home.
Do you like it?
You were late.
Ina got her award
and you missed it.
The new project, is, you know.
I'm just buried in work.
Do you even know what
you gave her for her birthday?
This necklace...
She wears it every day
since I told her it's from you.
Watch out!
You can't fix panic attacks
just by resting.
They've go to be treated.
Or the panic attacks
will continues
As for the medication,
set an alarm.
National Architecture Award
Don't worry, I'll be fine,
but Ina hasn't gotten
any better.
There's been no improvement?
She won't even
look me in the eye anymore.
The new environment and some
fresh air will do her good.
That's the reason
you moved out there.
I, I don't know what else
to do for her...
It's very frustrating.
As a last resort, you,
you could send her to that
Arts Camp I mentioned,
but you two
would be separated.
I'm not sure that it's
the best idea right now.
The truth is,
you need treatment.
I'm worried about you.
I'm more concerned about her.
So, what are you doing?
Are you having fun playing?
Look, Daddy.
Look how fast I am!
Well, show me!
I'm excited to see you run!
What? Just a minute.
Wasn't that all supposed
to be my job...
from start to finish?
But you're never here.
It's not because
I don't want to.
It's because of the kid!
Now you listen to me...
we signed a contract, you know?
Or am I wrong?
Okay, I'll come by...
I'll see you at the site.
Happy birthday to you,
you live in a zoo...
You look like a monkey,
and you smell like one, too!
Whoo!
Blow out the candles!
Or shall I do it?
No way!
- What did you wish for?
- IT's a secret!
- Aren't you going to tell me?
- No!
Ina!
What's wrong, honey?
Why did you scream just now?
I didn't scream, Daddy.
Is everything okay?
Uh-huh.
Can I come in for a while?
Yeah.
That's strange.
Are you sure you didn't scream?
Uh-huh.
Ina, where did you
get that doll?
It was in here.
- In there?
- Mm-hmm.
Let me see.
Do you remember?
I bought you a new doll
the other day?
I think you'll have more fun
playing with her.
Papa, can I also keep
this one?
It's dirty and belongs
to someone else.
Give it to me,
I'll throw it out.
I want to play
with both dolls.
That would be so much fun.
Are you really okay?
Mm-hmm.
Alright.
Time for bed.
Okay.
That was delicious.
Papa, can I go play
in my room now?
If you'd like.
I live our new house.
I even found a few friend.
That's great, Ina.
Great.
Why is Hyun-Sang
at the meeting?
If we both design it,
the whole concept will go
out the window. Huh?
What does he know
about art galleries?
He's never even designed
a little shack.
While you were away,
he did a gallery in Jeju.
He's hungry,
just like you used to be.
Honestly?
They really only wanted him.
I had to fight to get you
on this project.
That's bullshit.
The boss isn't happy either.
He says "No architect
can design anything,
if he's never seen
a building site.
I told you I'll be here.
But first, I have to find
a nanny for my daughter.
You've been saying that
for more than a month.
Time's running out.
Look over there.
Why is he here?
Huh... that's strange.
Why is Hyun-Sang here?
Could be coincidence.
So it's already been decided?
Huh?
No, why?
I will get this project done.
But without him.
Huh?
They have to choose between
me or him.
Wait...
Hold on.
Ina, what were you doing?
I wrote a song
as a surprise for you.
Do you want to hear it?
Ina.
I have to tell you something...
Remember, I told you about
designing a museum in Tongyeong?
Construction is starting
very soon.
That means I've got to spend
more time at the building site.
That's why I have hired a nanny
to take care of you. Okay?
- How long will it be, Dad?
- Maybe two months.
But I'll be home
every weekend to be with you.
Can I come along with you,
Daddy?
You know that I would love
to have you with me.
Construction sites are not
really good for kids...
I hope you understand.
If you help me out
and stay here,
I'll buy you a present.
Okay?
If you do what
you want anyway,
why did you ask?
Sweetheart,
I'm not doing whatever I want...
We have to find a way
to work together on this.
But if you never like
anything I suggest,
then I don't know
what I should do.
Ina, please just try
to understand my situation.
You don't want to be alone.
Let me think about it.
Okay?
Ina...
We'll talk about it again, okay?
Ina, it's late.
Go to bed.
Let me know by tomorrow
if you're coming or not.
What kind of therapy
does the art camp offer?
It starts with
Isolation Therapy.
How will she cope with that?
Separated from me,
and without her mother...
It won't be easy, but what
other choice do you have?
This is too much for you.
They only take a handful
of kids and expect a donation.
So, think about it.
Where are you going?
Ina, I have to got to work.
I'll be right back.
You wanted to talk to me...
Haven't you found
a present for me yet?
Ina,
let's talk about it tonight.
I ordered that doll for you.
It's coming from New York.
It'll be here soon.
Do you know how old I am?
I don't need
all these stupid dolls.
Ina...
You said you liked that doll.
And why are you talking
to me like that?
Why are you telling me
what I like?
Then you should tell me
what you want.
Absolutely nothing...
- And you call yourself a "Dad".
- What?
Ina!
Don't!
Don't! Don't!
Hello. I believe you're
looking for a nanny?
Hello. Yes. You know,
I, I was just on my way out.
It's 150 dollars a day.
Okay.
Do-Hyun,
this Art Camp donation,
how much are we talking about?
They are very well off.
The girl is in her room.
No wife...
Who knows.
It's possible she left him.
Anyway, he hid
all the expensive stuff.
What I found
is exactly my style.
This is my colleague.
- Hello.
- Mr. Kim.
- Hi.
- Pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
- Shall we go inside?
- Sure. Yes.
She won't stop screaming and
throwing shit around her room.
It doesn't matter what I cook.
She won't eat it.
She won't starve to death...
Shit!
You crazy little bitch!
She just started.
How can she quit
on her first day? Huh?
Don't give me that bullshit!
I'll be home this evening.
Make sure she stays
until I get there!
She took the money.
Tell her she has to finish
out the day.
Impossible.
I cannot leave.
Okay.
I spoke wit the camp manager.
You can send her there
next week!
I want to go, too.
Take me with you!
Come with us!
We'll take you away.
We'll take you away...
Come with us!
Child missing: Ina Yeon
(girl, 11 years old)
Thank you all.
That's not her.
She's been missing
for more than a month.
And you've come up with nothing.
It's frustrating.
We're not getting anywhere.
That nanny I hired.
Ina disappeared
right after she left.
Perhaps you could
question her again?
Well, we checked her car's
dash-cam video from that day,
and even had her take
a lie detector test.
I'm telling you, she's clean.
Go home and wait.
We'll call you.
You keep telling me
to go home and wait,
are you investigating this case,
or not?!
I understand you're upset,
but we are on the case.
- Ready.
- Okay.
Mr. Yeon,
please look into the camera.
Tell us about Ina.
Say whatever you'd like.
Hello, my name is
Sang-Won Yeon,
and this photo
is of my daughter, Ina.
She's 11 years old.
About a month ago...
Sh, she, she just disappeared.
I need your help to find her!
Please help!
If you know anything,
please contact the police.
We have checked
every security camera
and vehicle dash-cam within
a two-mile radius of Ina's home.
We have found
no trace of her at all.
Her mother died in a tragic
car accident last year.
The girl lived with her father.
According to witnesses,
the two were not
getting along very well.
While we were filming
in the family home,
we stumbled upon
numerous prescription drugs.
These are prescribed for
psychological disorders,
which implicates the treatment
of a serious condition.
The amount of medications
would be indicative
of a wide range of symptoms.
Yeah.
He was so fixated on work,
I was starting to get worried.
He never took any time off.
That probably made him
nervous and anxious.
Sadly, when a child disappears
it is often linked to problems
within the family or issues
with certain family members.
You may recall our report on
the disappearance of Min-Jin,
three years ago.
Upon closer inspection,
there appear to be many
obvious similarities
between these two cases.
In neither of them have the
police made any real progress.
Perhaps it is time to
re-examine these case
from a different angle.
A girl living with her father,
disappears from her home.
Where could she possibly be?
We are asking for information.
Is this "Behind the Story"?
Her father is a suspect.
Tsk.
No Internet Connection.
Ta-da!
Look!
A present from Daddy!
A butterfly necklace!
I love it!
It's so pretty!
You really like it?
Do you want to say
thank you to Daddy?
Thank you, Daddy.
Who are you?
Hello, sir.
I'm here for your internet.
Your front door was open.
Quite a big place
you've got here.
It'll take me a while
to find the problem.
Wow. This house is enormous.
Like a palace.
Are you an artist?
Or some kind of architect?
I would love to live
in a big house like this. Hmm.
But my family is poor.
Too bad.
It's not here.
How do you keep
this place clean? Huh?
This is too much for one person.
Do you have a cleaning lady?
It has a really high ceiling,
too.
I bet your heating bill
must be astronomical.
Did you know there are state
subsidies for solar panels etc.
It might be worth looking into.
You never know.
How much do you pay
per square foot here?
More than in Gangnam?
No idea.
You should ask a realtor that.
Can you just fix
the internet please?
Out here there are
cable problems.
That's nothing new.
So, the EMF is showing some...
I'm using an EMF detector
to find out what's going on.
EMF?
To check the internet?
Do you mind?
Sure.
Ah-ha.
Sorry,
can I have your business card?
What do you need
a business car for now?
I'm almost there.
I checked on the router
on the side of your house.
Someone cut the cable.
Huh?
What'd you say?
Didn't you call
an internet technician?
Hold on. Wait a minute.
Don't be like that.
Let's talk.
I can explain!
Who the hell are you?
Don't get me wrong.
I had to see for myself.
I'm here to help you.
You're from that TV show?
I won't talk to them again.
I'm calling the police.
Before she vanished,
did Ina seem different?
Act strange. Talk to herself?
Scream in front of the closet?
How did you know that?
Because Ina isn't the first
to vanish.
Thirty-two kids
have disappeared since '98.
I've been looking for ten years.
Just "Google" me under
"Heo Exorcist".
There are internet
blogs about me.
Professional Exorcism
I, I've also been on TV.
Exorcist Kyung-Hoon Heo
I am Korea's number 1 exorcist.
My skills made my reputation,
which, then made my prices...
about here.
Here, take a look at this.
They all disappeared
from their homes,
while playing,
doing their homework,
while they were sleeping.
They all vanished
without a trace.
They made these drawings.
All of them are of a child.
About 20 years ago,
a girl named Hyun-Soo
disappeared just like Ina.
Her parents conducted a ritual
to find out if their daughter
was still alive.
You've seen her, right?
That's my mom.
Some of the other children's
parents mentioned
that they had seen her.
I think she was trying
to warn them,
to protect their children.
Shall I go on?
She killed my mother,
took the children.
Now, she has Ina as well.
That's her.
The source of all this,
a demonic child.
How can I believe you?
Huh?
Is this real? Huh?
A ghost stole my child?
You're ritual is a con.
You think I'm stupid?
Get out!
Out!
So, you don't believe me.
Okay.
But I'm the only one
who believe you.
Everyone else thinks
you killed her.
If you don't hurry,
your daughter
will be lost forever.
Wait.
Can you really find her?
Yeah.
Mourning someone lost
keeps their spirit in the
underworld for 49 days.
The so-called
49 Day Memorial Rite.
It's been explained in the
movie "Along With the Gods."
Haven't you seen it?
No, I haven't.
And I thought you had
an education.
In any case,
Ina's got only 3 days left.
No more.
Oh.
This sensor detects objects
that emit wavelengths
far beyond quantum mechanics.
Basically, it detects ghosts.
So, where exactly is
Ina right now?
In the realm of the dead.
We call it the dark realm.
Uh-huh...
- Let me show you.
- Don't tear that.
Look here!
Here are the living.
Here are the dead.
Each has it's own realm.
This fold separates them.
They exist together,
side by side,
but because of this border,
they cannot see each other.
However, once their
respective frequencies
start to synchronize,
they can see each other
and move between
the two realms.
Just like in "Interstellar".
A shamanic exorcism
disentangles those
two frequencies.
Some call it "Being possessed".
It happens a lot. Which is why
I have to protect myself.
The most evil spirits
like the demon we're after,
Synchronization
find people that are
in sync with them,
and then pull them
into their realm.
With time,
they lose their memory
and they're only left
with evil.
They become the Blinded.
Once you look into their eyes,
you're trapped
and get sucked
into their realm.
They're tortured souls.
What do I have to do
to find her?
We just have to trap
the demon,
bargain or beat her,
whatever works.
Demonic children
are attracted by dolls.
When they touch these straw
dolls soaked in my blood,
it excites them.
It's like a trap.
Father of all,
we beseech you on behalf of Ina,
and for all those whom we love
but see no longer.
Grant to them eternal rest.
Let your light
perpetually shine upon them.
May her soul be rescued from
the souls of all the departed,
through the mercy of God.
These charms create a boundary.
They're worth a fortune
and their value keeps going up.
Yep, they're really expensive.
Insanely expensive.
So... Pay attention,
she'll be here soon.
Put this on.
Have you tried these noodles?
They taste home-made,
with fried tofu.
Who cares about fried tofu?
Does this really work?
Of course.
Don't worry.
Just be patient.
Maybe she's on to us?
She hasn't come?
Wait... I hear something.
Oh, that's Ina's violin.
- Ow!
- Ah, my ears...
Uh...
She has some nerve.
Was Ina here?
I'm not sure about that.
L... let's try it again,
I'll drench a big doll
with blood.
She is really something else.
Tell me...
Who's Ina's favorite singer?
BTS? Blackpink?
Some kid's band?
You don't know?
Who is her best friend?
I see.
You don't know much
about her, do you?
Do you ever talk to her?
That's not good.
You know,
I really hate silence.
I also hate too much talk.
But I hate silence the most.
So, what would you
like me to call you?
Call me whatever you'd like.
Mm.
How about...
"Mr. Yeon."
What do you think?
Or, since you hired me,
should I call you "Boss"?
I think I'd prefer "Mr. Yeon."
And what would you like me
to call you?
"Director."
They work the hardest.
I'm really thirsty!
I'll go check your fridge.
Director!
Daddy!
Mr. Yeon, close your eyes!
Close them now!
We didn't set the trap,
she did.
The Blinded can only see
when your eyes are open.
So keep them shut and very
slowly get out of there!
Don't move now.
Be very still.
And now,
do exactly what I say!
Lie flat on the floor
and slowly turn to your right.
Now go to the left!
Left!
Mr. Yeon, stop!
Don't move a muscle.
Don't move!
Stay right there!
You're almost there.
Just hang on.
Shit.
Just stay still.
You mustn't move.
I'll be with you in a second!
Hang in there!
Oh, Jesus.
Get out of there, Mr. Yeon!
Just get out!
Our Father,
which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Turn back the evil
upon my foes;
in your faithfulness
destroy them.
Freely will I offer you
sacrifice;
I will praise your name,
Lord, for its goodness,
Because from all distress
you have rescued me,
and my eyes look down
upon my enemies.
Glory be to the Father.
You're...
Missing: Myung-Jin Cho (11)
Myung-Jin Cho.
Mr. Heo!
What happened?
Here, let me help you.
That was embarrassing.
- It was Myung-Lin.
- Myung-Jin?
Operating Room
Child missing!
Any hint helps!
Missing: Myung-Jin Cho (11)
Chungcheong Province,
Jujin District, near Gyebaek
Gyebaek Real Estate
Ah, I'm not sure.
Got another photo?
Just this one.
Looks like an ex-con.
Really, did he steal
money from you?
His child disappeared.
Oh, really?
So sorry,
didn't mean it like that.
Wait.
A missing child?
Hmm.
It may be that Sangdong guy.
There's this guy living
on Mount Sangdong alone. Oh
He has all this strange stuff
in the woods around his house.
I heard about his
child disappearing.
Oh my son.
Don't forget.
For your mother.
- Defibrillator!
- Yes, doctor!
Hello?
Is anybody home?
Who are you?
Sorry.
Are you Myung-Jin's father?
Please leave!
Can I ask you some questions
about your daughter?
Are you a cop?
No, I'm not.
My daughter,
she also disappeared.
I think Myung-Jin
had something to do with it.
She disappeared
while she was asleep
in the room next to ours.
My wife went out to for her,
but she never returned.
I searched her for ten years,
then I gave up.
I spent the next ten years
trying to forget her.
And I have forgotten.
Now leave.
Before she disappeared,
did something happen?
It may sound strange,
but did her personality change?
Did she stand in front
of a closet and talk to herself?
Why do you think I live alone
in the mountains?
I don't want to be confronted
with children.
That's why I live secluded
like a hermit.
I'm sorry.
Have you ever seen,
or recall this doll?
Hey, hey!
How on Earth?
This is impossible.
Why are you here?
What do you want from me?
Stay away!
I don't want to die!
You can't take me!
Never!
This can't be here.
I have to burn it, quick!
Oh, God.
Oh.
Papa!
Myung... Myung-Jin...
Hello?
Darling,
it's alright.
What are you doing?
Just wait.
You go on ahead
and wait for us.
Sir, please...
I will...
be right there.
Daddy! Daddy!
Please, let me out! Please!
I'm so afraid!
Mom! Dad! Mommy!
Mom, let me, let me out!
More than 1,000 shops
have closed or are for sale.
Many are offering huge discounts
to liquidate their stock.
- In Seoul alone...
- Please, let me out!
Mom! Dad!
Please, let me out.
I'm sorry!
Please, Dad!
I'm scared.
Mom! Mom!
Mama, can you hear me?
Mom!
Please, let me out!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please, just let me out!
Daddy!
Myung-Jin!
Just because you breathe
doesn't mean you're alive.
Please, help me, Daddy!
In our next life,
we'll be a happy family,
without debts.
Papa, I...
I am really sorry.
I didn't mean it, Daddy.
I swear.
This is no life.
We're better off
if we're all dead.
I'm so afraid!
I'm sorry!
Daddy!
Let me out.
No.
No, no! Please!
No! Daddy!
Please, let me out!
I'm sorry! Please! Daddy!
Daddy! Please!
I, I'm sorry!
Just let me out!
Please, Daddy!
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus,
omnis satanica potestas,
omnis incursio infernalis
adversarii,
omnis legio, omnis congregatio
et secta diabolica.
Help me!
I saw Myung-Jin's death.
Your frequencies
were synchronized.
That's why you saw
her memories.
Her rage turned into a demon.
She's gathered other kids,
that had suffered like she did.
It makes sense,
if you think about it.
You've neglected Ina.
Just be honest.
Your work was always
more important to you.
Basically, you wanted her
to go away.
Get to the point.
Children instinctively know
if someone truly loves them,
or not.
Buying her a doll or a toy,
doesn't change that.
The missing kids
all share one thing:
Their parents either physically
or emotionally abused
or neglected them.
Just like with Ina.
How terrible it must have been
for her to live with a father,
who didn't want
to be with her.
Imagine how lonely she felt!
Her soul cried out in pain,
and Myung-Jin heard her.
It's my fault she's gone.
- Mr. Heo.
- Hang on wait.
Let me finish.
The frequency.
I see her
when we're in sync.
Does that mean
I can cross over to her?
Step into her realm?
If you are in sync,
then yes.
During my panic attack,
you said I was in sync
with Myung-Jin.
Does that mean
I can meet Ina?
What are you planning?
Let me cross over.
Our time is short.
Absolutely not.
It's too dangerous.
You could get killed.
So what.
I don't care if it's dangerous.
We have no other choice.
Got a better idea?
Help me get to her!
You have no idea
what you're asking.
You could lose your way
on the other side. Hmm?
This could destroy
my career as an exorcist.
What you're asking,
is impossible.
Sorry for bringing up money,
but I will pay you
whatever you ask for.
I have to try.
I have to get to Ina before
she's completely out of time.
Help me get to her.
I will use the ritual
to protect you,
but you'll only have
30 minutes.
If you don't get back...
Well, I don't need to tell you
about the Blinded.
You'll turn into one of them.
I understand.
Let's try it.
You're the boss.
How can you trigger
a panic attack?
It's a strange question.
You have to trust me.
Just tell me how.
I need to know.
Myung-Jin Cho (11)
A large dose of caffeine pills
can cause a panic attack,
and in a worst-case scenario,
death.
So be very careful.
You've been warned.
Are you ready?
They'll kick in
any minute now.
You are stepping into
Myung-Jin's realm.
Anything could happen.
She'll do everything
in her power to stop you.
You must be aware of that.
Ina.
I'll bring her back with me.
Just stay alive,
so you can pay me
really well.
Be worth it.
This fire is linked
to your soul.
When your time runs out,
or if you die,
the fire will extinguish.
Sicut déficit fumus defíciant;
sicut fluit cera a fácia ígnis,
sic péreant peccatóres
a fácia Dei.
Give me the strength
o heaven,
to guide this soul through
the valley of death
and return in peace to your
loving countenance.
Prínceps gloriosíssine coeléstis
milítiae,
sancte Míchael Archángele,
defénde nos in proélio
et colluctatióne,
quae nobis est advérsus
príncipes et potestá...
Seung-Hee!
Wait!
Seung-Hee...
Look what you've done to Ina!
Ina is dying.
And now...
Die!
...Defénde nos
in proélio et colluctatióne,
quae nobis est advérsus
ete potestátes,
advérsus múndi rectóres
tenebrárum hárum.
Give me strength o heaven,
to guide this soul through
the valley of death
and to return him in peace
to your loving countenance.
Let them be turned back
and be confounded
that devise evil against him.
Give me strength of heaven,
to guide this soul through
the valley of death
and to return him in peace
to your loving countenance.
Let them be confounded
and ashamed that
seek after his soul.
Ina!
Seung-Hee...
Are you okay?
Baby.
Ina!
You have to protect Ina.
Always.
Seung-Hee, Seung-Hee.
Darling!
No! Seung-Hee!
Ina!
Why are you here?
Myung-Jin, I came to get Ina.
Why?
This is what you wanted!
Did you want to get rid of her,
or not?
The Art Camp donation,
how much are we talking about?
In those days,
well, I, I was...
Ina will soon be living
here with us.
Myung-Jin!
Please, let her go!
Please let her
come back with me!
Myung-Jin!
I saw what happened.
I saw the closet.
That's why you've brought
those kids here. And Ina.
The last thing you heard on
that terrible day, was your...
Stop talking!
This is no life.
We're better off
if we're all dead.
Do you trust me?
Mama!
Mama...
I want to live!
It's us.
We adults are to blame.
It's all my fault.
Don't lie to me!
Oh my son,
don't forget,
look for your mother!
Mom!
Ina!
Help me!
Kill him.
Ina, don't listen to her!
The Spirits shall live
where they belong,
and the Gods
where the Gods reside.
Ina, please!
Ina!
Myung-Jin!
Here you are, my darling!
Mama?
Everything you went through.
You must have been so afraid.
And I couldn't protect you.
I'm so sorry, my darling.
Oh, Myung-Jin.
I've been waiting for you.
- Mama...
- Myung-Jin.
Now you can finally rest!
Ina.
Ina!
Oh.
Myung-Jin!
Mom!
Mama!
Oh, Mama!
Ma!
Mama!
Mama! Mama!
Ma!
Myung-Jin.
Mr. Yeon, hurry up!
We're running out of time!
Myung-Jin.
I am so sorry.
Ina!
Ina, wake up!
Ina...
Papa.
Daddy, I want to go home.
Ina, we're going home.
Let's go home.
We're going home.
Mr. Yeon!
She still doesn't remember?
I hope she never will.
How's the new house?
It's big enough for us.
It's cozy.
That's great.
If you use your credit card,
I'll have to add on 10 percent.
If you post about me online,
you get a free charm.
Total: $175,000
Well...
Ina!
- Bye.
- Bye!
Papa...
- Over here!
- Hop in, young lady!
Don't worry, darling,
he's alright.
Nice try, my friend.
Remove a zero or two.
Maybe I'll buy a ball
for my new friend.
Oh, stop it!
You don't have any friends!
Yes, I do.
Really
Where? Show me.
Subtitles by explosiveskull